Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Legal Department microfilmed entertainment contracts, 1924-1957 RL.11870
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Contracts for Broadcasting, 1929-1949; undated; 1
  - Lever Brothers--Lux Radio Theatre, 1931-1942; 36
    - The Fighting 69th--Consent, 1942 Apr. 6 (Film-reel 161)
    - The Gay Sisters--Consent, 1942 Nov. 23 (Film-reel 161)
    - The Goose Hangs High, 1934 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 112)
    - The Great Lie--Consent, 1942 Mar. 2 (Film-reel 161)
    - The Lady Eve--Consent, 1942 Mar. 9 (Film-reel 161)
    - The Letter--Consent, 1938 May 23; 1941 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Man Who Played God--Consent, 1938 Mar. 21 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Moon's Our Home--Consent, 1941 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Nervous Wreck, 1934 Nov. 11 (Film-reel 112)
    - The Pied Piper--Consent, 1942 Dec. 21 (Film-reel 161)
    - The Princess Comes Across--Consent, 1938 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Rage of Paris--Consent, 1940 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Rains Came--Consent, 1940 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Scarlet Pimpernel--Consent, 1938 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Show Off--Consent, 1940 May 23 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Show Off--Teletypes, 1940 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Sisters--Consent, 1939 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Star Maker--Consent, 1939 Oct. 23 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Under Pup--Consent, 1940 Apr. 15 (Film-reel 160)
    - The Westerner--Consent, 1940 Sept. 23 (Film-reel 160)
    - Thelma Hubbard, 1938 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 160)
    - Theodora Goes Wild--Consent, 1938 June 13 (Film-reel 160)
    - They Drive By Night--Consent, 1941 June 2 (Film-reel 160)
    - Third Finger, Left Hand--Consent, 1941 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 161)
    - This Above All--Consent, 1942 Sept. 14 (Film-reel 161)
    - Thomas Hughes, 1939 Feb. 13-Dec. 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Thomas Mitchell, 1938 Jan. 24; 1940 May 6 (Film-reel 160)
    - Thunder in the City--Consent, 1938 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 160)
    - Til We Meet Again--Consent, 1940 June 10 (Film-reel 160)
    - To Mary with Love--Consent, 1942 Nov. 16 (Film-reel 161)
    - To the Ladies--Consent, 1940 July 8 (Film-reel 160)
    - Tom, Dick and Harry--Consent, 1941 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 161)
    - Tommy Mitchell, 1939 May 19 (Film-reel 160)
    - Tovarich--Consent, 1939 May 15 (Film-reel 160)
    - Trade Winds--Consent, 1940 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 160)
    - Travis Banton, 1938 Apr. 18 (Film-reel 160)
    - Tyrone Power, 1940 Nov. 18 (Film-reel 160)
    - Tyrone Power, 1941 Oct. 20; 1942 Sept. 14 (Film-reel 161)
    - Una Merkel, 1940 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 160)
    - Unfinished--Consent, 1941 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 161)
    - Untamed--Correspondence, 1940 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 160)
    - Vagabond King--Consent, 1938 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 160)
    - Van Johnson, 1942 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 161)
    - Veronica Lake, 1942 Mar. 30; Nov. 9 (Film-reel 161)
    - Victor Mature, 1940 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 160)
    - Vigil in the Night--Consent, 1940 May 27 (Film-reel 160)
    - Virginia Bruce, 1940 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 160)
    - Virginia Bruce, 1941 Dec. 8; 1942 Oct. 19 (Film-reel 161)
    - Virginia City--Consent, 1941 May 26 (Film-reel 160)
    - Virginia Wiedler, 1940 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 160)
    - Viva Villa--Consent, 1938 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 160)
    - Viva Villa--Teletypes, 1940 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 160)
    - Vivacious Lady--Consent, 1941 Jan. 6 (Film-reel 160)
    - W.C. Fields, 1938 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 160)
    - Wake Island--Consent, 1942 Oct. 26 (Film-reel 161)
    - Wallace Beery, 1938-1941 (Film-reel 160)
    - Wallace Beery, 1942 June 29 (Film-reel 161)
    - Wallace Clark, 1938 May 9 (Film-reel 160)
    - Walter B. Pitkin, 1939 June 26 (Film-reel 160)
    - Walter Brennan--Consent, 1940 Sept. 23 (Film-reel 160)
    - Walter Catlett, 1939 Dec. 25 (Film-reel 160)
    - Walter Connolly, 1934 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 112)
    - Walter Connolly, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 160)
    - Walter Huston, 1934 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 112)
    - Walter Huston, 1938 May 23 (Film-reel 160)
    - Walter Pidgeon, 1941 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 160)
    - Walter Pidgeon, 1942 (Film-reel 161)
    - Walter Wanger, 1938 Feb. 21 (Film-reel 160)
    - War Against Mrs. Hadley--Consent, 1942 Dec. 7 (Film-reel 161)
    - Warren Williams, 1939 May 1; 1941 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 160)
    - Wayne Morris, 1938 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 160)
    - Werner Baxter, 1941 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 160)
    - What Every Woman Knows, 1934 Oct. 21 (Film-reel 112)
    - Wife, Husband and Friend--Consent, 1941 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 160)
    - Will Hays, 1938 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 160)
    - William de Mille, 1940 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 160)
    - William Frawley, 1938 Jan. 10; Apr. 18 (Film-reel 160)
    - William Gargan, 1939 Mar. 6; 1941 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 160)
    - William Holden, 1940 May 6 (Film-reel 160)
    - William Holden, 1942 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 161)
    - William Powell, 1938-1940 (Film-reel 160)
    - William Powell, 1941 Nov. 3; 1942 Oct. 5 (Film-reel 161)
    - Wings of the Navy--Consent, 1940 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 160)
    - Wuthering Heights--Consent, 1939 Sept. 18; 1940 Nov. 4 (Film-reel 160)
    - You Can't Take It With You--Consent, 1939 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 160)
    - Young Tom Edison--Consent, 1940 Dec. 23 (Film-reel 160)
    - Zazu Pitts, 1939 July 10 (Film-reel 160)
    - Zezebel--Consent, 1940 Nov. 25 (Film-reel 160)
    - Zoe Atkins, 1938 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 160)
  - Libby McNeill & Libby, 1930-1942; 37
    - Carl McCullough, 1930 (Film-reel 112)
    - Irving Crump, 1934 Oct. 1-1935 May 26 (Film-reel 112)
    - Pauline Haggard, 1930 Oct. 21-Dec. 30 (Film-reel 112)
    - Ray Perkins, 1930-1942 (Film-reel 112)
  - London Office, 1937-1938; 38
    - Cappy Barra's Harmonica Ensemble, 1937 (Film-reel 112)
    - Chester Morris, 1938 (Film-reel 112)
    - Connie Boswell, 1937 (Film-reel 112)
    - Doris Weston, 1937 (Film-reel 112)
    - George Raft, 1937 (Film-reel 112)
    - Ida Lupino, 1937 (Film-reel 112)
    - Pat O'Brien, 1938 (Film-reel 112)
    - The Foursome, 1938 (Film-reel 112)
    - Vass Family, 1937 (Film-reel 112)
  - Lux Radio Theatre--Shell Chateau, 1936; 39
    - James Cagney--Shore Leave, 1936 Feb. 14 (Film-reel 160)
  - Lux--Chase & Sanborn--Kraft Music Hall--Baker's Program, 1938; 40
    - Joan Bennett, 1938 Jan. 18 (Film-reel 160)
  - Lux--Shell Chateau--Kraft Hour, 1936; 41
    - Bette Davis, 1936 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 160)
  - Nash Motor Company--Radio Programs, 1936-1937; 42
    - Amanda Randolph, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Anthony Galla Rini, 1936 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Belle Baker, 1937 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Billy Jones and Ernie Hare, 1936 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Buck and Bubbles, 1937 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Captain Cornelius F. Willemse, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Charlotte Symons, 1936 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Conrad Mayo, 1936 Dec. 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - Crane Calder and Chorus, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Cyril Von Baumann, 1937 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Dorothea Brande, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Dr. William Moulton Marston, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Earl Rossman, 1937 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Edith Lorard, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Efrem Zimbalist, 1936 Dec. 5; 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - Floyd Gibbons, 1936 Oct. 3-1937 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Folios, 1937 May-June (Film-reel 138)
    - Frederick Jagel, 1936 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 138)
    - Giovanni Martinelli, 1936 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Grace Moore, 1937 Mar. 20-June 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Greta Stueckgold, 1936 Oct.3 (Film-reel 138)
    - Helen Jepson, 1937 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Henry Burbig, 1936 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Irene Bordoni, 1936 Oct. 17; 31 (Film-reel 138)
    - Isaac Van Grove, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Joe Cook, 1936 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 138)
    - Joe Sodja, 1936 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Joe White, 1936 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - John McCormack, 1936 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 138)
    - Josephine Antoine, 1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Kate Smith, 1937 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Lawrence Stallings, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Loire Brophy, 1937 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Lotte Lehmann, 1937 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Lupe Velez, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Mildred Dilling, 1936 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 138)
    - Mrs. William Harkness Jr., 1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Natalie Bodanya, 1936 Dec. 12; 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Olsen and Johnson, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Queena Mario, 1936 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 138)
    - Richard Bonelli, 1936 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 138)
    - Roy Smeck, 1936 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ruth Breton, 1936 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Sheila Barrett, 1937 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Sophie Tucker, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Stepin Fetchit, 1937 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 138)
      Stage name of African American vaudevillian Lincoln Theodore Monroe Andrew Perry (1902-1985), who had a successful film career. Considered the first African American actor to receive a film credit, and the first African American millionaire actor.
    - Stoopnagle and Bud, 1937 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Charioteers, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Don Cossacks, 1936 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Mills Brothers, 1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Minnervitch Gang, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Southernaires, 1937 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 138)
      African American vocal group formed in 1929
    - The Three Marshalls, 1937 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Tito Schipa, 1936 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Vincent Lopez, 1936 Oct. 3-1937 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Walter B. Putkin, 1937 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Walter O'Keefe, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - William McCaffery, 1936 Oct. 31 (Film-reel 138)
    - Willie and Eugene Howard, 1937 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Yoichi Hiraoka, 1937 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 138)
  - National Dairy Association--Programs Folios and Contracts, 1936-1937; 43
    - 5 Minutes from the Station--Permission, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Abbey Players--Rising of the Moon, 1937 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Albert Spalding, 1937 May 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - Aline McMahon, 1937 June 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Arthur Donovan, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Claude Rains, 1937 July 18 (Film-reel 138)
    - Comrades in Arms--Consent, 1937 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Conrad Nagel, 1937 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - Cornelia Otis Skinner, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Dennis King, 1937 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 138)
    - Donald Dickson, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Doris Hare, 1937 May 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Edith Barrett, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Edward Trevor, 1937 July 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Efrem Zimbalist, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Elissa Landi, 1937 Aug. 22 (Film-reel 138)
    - Enter Madame--Consent, 1937 June 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Erin O'Brien Moore, 1937 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ethel Merman, 1937 Jan. 16; Apr. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ezio Pinza, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Frances Farmer, 1937 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - Francis Lederer, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Gertrude Lawrence, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Harold Vermilyca, 1937 July 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Helen Rowe, 1937 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Henry Fonda, 1937 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Henry Hull, 1937 June 13; July 25 (Film-reel 138)
    - Her Majesty the King--Consent, 1937 July 11 (Film-reel 138)
    - Howard & Shelton, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ian Keith, 1937 July 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Interference--Consent, 1937 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jean Muir, 1937 July 11 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jimmy Durante, 1937 May 23; 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Joe Di Maggio, 1937 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 138)
    - John McCormack, 1937 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 138)
    - Joseph Shildkraut, 1937 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 138)
    - Kate Smith, 1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Lanny Ross, 1936 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Lauritz Melchior, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Margaret McCrae, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Marta Abba, 1937 June 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Mary Boland, 1937 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Maurice Evans, 1937 May 15; Oct. 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - May Robson, 1937 July 11 (Film-reel 138)
    - Michael Strange, 1937 May 15 (Film-reel 138)
    - Mischa Levitski, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Mitzi Green, 1937 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Moonshine--Consent, 1937 Aug. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Mrs. Baffin Buys Tickets for the Coronation--Permission, 1937 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Mrs. Muggins--Permission, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Nancy McCord, 1937 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 138)
    - Niela Goodelle, 1937 July 25 (Film-reel 138)
    - Osgood Perkins, 1937 June 27 (Film-reel 138)
    - Outward Bound--Consent, 1937 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - Patsy Kelly, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Peggy Conklin, 1937 July 25 (Film-reel 138)
    - Pepper Martin's Missouri Madcats, 1937 May 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Polly Moran, 1937 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Reginald Gardiner, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Richard Cortez, 1937 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Robert E. Dolan, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Roland Young, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Sally Eilers, 1937 Aug. 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Sheila Barrett, 1937 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 138)
    - Shirley Booth, 1937 Apr. 17; June 13 (Film-reel 138)
    - Sing Me a Love Song--Permission, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Stanley Winthrop Shaw, 1937 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 138)
    - Sybil Jason, 1937 May 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Girl--Consent, 1937 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Harp--Consent, 1937 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Highway Man--Permission, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - The New Yorkers, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Tell-Tale Heart--Permisison, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Third Angle--Consent, 1937 Aug. 29 (Film-reel 138)
    - Tom Howard, George Shelton, 1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - Vagabond King--Consent, 1937 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 138)
    - Valley Forge--Consent, 1937 July 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Vincent Price, 1937 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 138)
    - Vivian Della Chiesa, 1937 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 138)
    - Waldo Mayo, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Walter Damrosch, 1937 May 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - Walter Humpden, 1937 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 138)
    - Wynn Murray, 1937 Aug. 1 (Film-reel 138)
    - Yascha Bunchuk and Band, 1937 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 138)
    - Zasu Pitts, 1937 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 138)
  - National Dairy Association--Sealtest System Laboratories, 1936-1937; 44
    - Contract with Ayer, 1936 Aug. 14 (Film-reel 138)
      Assignment of Ayer's contract from Sealtest to J. Walter Thompson
    - Donald Dickson, 1937 Jan. 30-July 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Ferde Grofe, 1936 Oct. 17-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
      Includes copy of notice of assignment of Ayer's NBC contract
    - Folios, 1936 Dec. 12; 19 (Film-reel 138)
    - James L. Saphier, 1937 Feb. 13-Oct. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - James Melton, 1937 Feb. 10-Oct. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Jane Pickens, 1936-1937 (Film-reel 138)
    - June Collyer, 1937 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 151)
    - Leonard T. Holton, 1936 Oct. 17-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Letter from Seatltest switching program to J. Walter Thompson, 1936 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Local 802, 1936 June 4 (Film-reel 138)
    - Lucia Graeser, 1937 Jan. 30-Apr. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Nelson Case, 1936 Nov. 7-Dec. 26 (Film-reel 138)
    - Notice of claim from Local 802 on Ferde Grofe, 1936 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 138)
    - Raymond Knight, 1936 Dec. 5-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Robert E. Dolan, 1937 Feb. 6-Oct. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Stuart Churchill, 1936 Oct. 17-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Stuart Erwin, 1937 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 151)
    - The New Yorkers, 1936 Oct. 17-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - The Tune Twisters, 1936 Oct. 17-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Tom Howard, 1936 Dec. 5-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Tom Howard, George Shelton, 1937 Apr. 17-Oct. 10 (Film-reel 138)
    - Walter Cassel, 1936 Oct. 17-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Walter O'Keefe, 1936 Oct. 17-1937 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 138)
    - Wynn Murray, 1937 Aug. 15-Oct. 10 (Film-reel 138)
  - Nestle, 1930-1934; 45
    - Adele Astaire, 1931 Dec. 4 (Film-reel 112)
    - Alice Boulden, 1931 Mar. 13 (Film-reel 112)
    - Allan Joslyn, 1930 Sept. 5-1931 May 29 (Film-reel 112)
    - Allan Joslyn, 1931 June 5-1932 Sept. 30 (Film-reel 112)
    - Baby Rose Marie, 1931 July 24 (Film-reel 112)
    - Basil Rathbone, 1931 Nov. 27 (Film-reel 112)
    - Beatrice Joy, 1931 Mar. 20 (Film-reel 112)
    - Beatrice Lillie, 1931 Mar. 27; Apr. 24 (Film-reel 112)
    - Bella Baker, 1930-1932 (Film-reel 112)
    - Bernardo de Pace, 1931 Aug. 28 (Film-reel 112)
    - Bernice Claire, 1931 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 112)
    - Bettina Hall, 1931-1932 (Film-reel 112)
    - Buddy Doyle, 1932 June 3-Aug. 26 (Film-reel 112)
    - Charlie King, 1930 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 112)
    - Chic Farmer, 1931-1933 May 26 (Film-reel 112)
    - Clyce Doerr Saxophone Octet, 1931 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 112)
    - Del Stargers, 1931 Mar. 27 (Film-reel 112)
    - Dennis King, 1930 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 112)
    - Don Bestor, 1933 Aug. 25-1934 Mar. 30 (Film-reel 112)
    - Dorothy Stone, 1931 Apr. 17 (Film-reel 112)
    - Duncan Sisters, 1930 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 112)
    - Elizabeth Lennox, 1931 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 112)
    - Ethel Merman, 1930 Nov. 21 (Film-reel 112)
    - Ethel Shutta, 1933 Aug. 25-1934 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 112)
    - Everett Marshall, 1932 Feb. 12 (Film-reel 112)
    - Fanny Brice, 1931 Jan. 9 (Film-reel 112)
    - Frances Williams, 1930-1931 (Film-reel 112)
    - Frank Luther and Carson Roberson, 1931 July 31 (Film-reel 112)
    - Frank Millan, 1931 May 22 (Film-reel 112)
    - Fred Astaire, 1931 Sept. 18 (Film-reel 112)
    - George Hysan, 1931 May 1 (Film-reel 112)
    - George Jessel, 1931 Oct. 23 (Film-reel 112)
    - George Meader, 1932 Apr. 15 (Film-reel 112)
    - Ginger Rogers, 1930 Sept. 19; Dec. 26 (Film-reel 112)
    - Grace Hayes, 1930 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 112)
    - Guy Robertson, 1931 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 112)
    - Harry Richman, 1931 Oct. 9 (Film-reel 112)
    - Helen Gordon, 1931 May 15 (Film-reel 112)
    - Helen Kane, 1930 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 112)
    - Helen Lynd, 1932 Jan. 29 (Film-reel 112)
    - Helen Morgan, 1930 Sept. 5 (Film-reel 112)
    - Howard Marsh, 1931 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 112)
    - Irene Bordoni, 1930 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 112)
    - J. Harold Murray, 1932 Mar. 11 (Film-reel 112)
    - Jack Haley, 1932 Apr. 29 (Film-reel 112)
    - James Wallington, 1932 Oct. 7 (Film-reel 112)
    - Janet Reade, 1932 Apr. 8 (Film-reel 112)
    - Jeanne Aubert, 1931 Apr. 10 (Film-reel 112)
    - Jeannette Loff, 1931 Oct. 2 (Film-reel 112)
    - John Fogarty, 1931 Aug. 21 (Film-reel 112)
    - John White, 1931 June 19; 26 (Film-reel 112)
    - Johnny Marvin, 1930 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 112)
    - Joseph Macauley, 1932 Apr. 1 (Film-reel 112)
    - Joseph White, 1931 July 10 (Film-reel 112)
    - Julie Gundersen, 1931 May 8 (Film-reel 112)
    - Lee Morse, 1931 Aug. 7 (Film-reel 112)
    - Leonard Joy, 1931 Dec. 18-1933 May 26 (Film-reel 112)
    - Lillian Roth, 1930 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 112)
    - Louise Groody, 1931 May 29 (Film-reel 112)
    - Madge Kennedy, 1931 Sept. 11 (Film-reel 112)
    - Margaret McKee, 1931 (Film-reel 112)
    - Mario Chamlee, 1932 Sept. 9 (Film-reel 112)
    - Marion Harris, 1930 Dec. 5; 1931 Nov. 6 (Film-reel 112)
    - Mary Lawlor, 1931 Sept. 4 (Film-reel 112)
    - Mitzi Green, 1932 Apr. 22 (Film-reel 112)
    - Nat Brusiloff, 1931 June 5-1932 May 27 (Film-reel 112)
    - Nick Lucas, 1930 Nov. 7 (Film-reel 112)
    - Norma Terris, 1931 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 112)
    - Oscar Shaw, 1931 Nov. 13 (Film-reel 112)
    - Phil Ohman and Victor Ardan, 1931 Mar. 6; 13 (Film-reel 112)
    - Phil Spitalny and orchestra, 1932-1933 (Film-reel 112)
    - Robert E. Dolan, 1934 Apr. 6-Aug. 17 (Film-reel 112)
    - Ross MacLean, 1931 Dec. 11; 1932 July 1-Sept. 2 (Film-reel 112)
    - Roy Smeck, 1931 July 17 (Film-reel 112)
    - Ruth Etting, 1931 Jan. 30; Oct. 16 (Film-reel 112)
    - Sophie Tucker, 1931 Dec. 18 (Film-reel 112)
    - South Sea Islanders, 1931 July 3 (Film-reel 112)
    - Sylvia Froos, 1932 Mar. 25 (Film-reel 112)
    - Venute and Lange, 1931 Aug. 14 (Film-reel 112)
    - Victor Moore, 1932 Feb. 5; May 6-27 (Film-reel 112)
    - Victor Moore, 1932 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 146)
    - Vivian Hart, 1931 Oct. 30 (Film-reel 112)
    - Viviene Segal, 1931 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 112)
    - Walter Glass, 1930 Oct. 3; Oct 10 1930 (Film-reel 112)
    - Walter O'Keefe, 1933 Aug. 25-1934 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 112)
    - William Gaxton, 1932 Jan. 8 (Film-reel 112)
    - Willis and Eugene Howard, 1932 Mar. 4 (Film-reel 112)
    - Winnie Lightner, 1930 Oct. 31 (Film-reel 112)
    - Zelma O'Neal, 1930 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 112)
  - Northam Warren--Cutex, 1935; 46
    - Folios, 1935 Sept. 9-Dec. 23 (Film-reel 151)
    - In the Dark--Consent, 1935 (Film-reel 151)
    - Niela Goodelle, 1935 (Film-reel 151)
    - Phil Baker and Orchestra, 1933-1934 (Film-reel 151)
  - Northam Warren--Odorono, 1934; 47
    - Marley R. Sherris, 1934 (Film-reel 151)
  - P. Ballantine and Sons, 1941-1949; 48
    - American Laughter--Consent, 1941 Oct. 24-Nov. 7 (Film-reel 152)
    - Ballad of the Harp Weaver--Consent, 1941 Sept. 19 (Film-reel 152)
    - Bela Lugosi, 1942 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 152)
    - Billie Burke, 1942 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 152)
    - Billy Gilbert, 1942 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 152)
    - Boxing radio and television, 1948 (Film-reel 442)
    - Brenda Joyce, 1942 May 5 (Film-reel 152)
    - Charles Judels, 1942 Feb. 27 (Film-reel 152)
    - Charles Laughton, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 152)
    - Chester Morris, 1942 May 19 (Film-reel 152)
    - Donald Crisp, 1942 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 152)
    - Dorothy Lamour, 1942 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 152)
    - Edna May Oliver, 1942 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 152)
    - Edward Arnold, 1942 (Film-reel 152)
    - Edward Everett Horton, 1942 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 152)
    - Folios, 1941-1943 (Film-reel 152)
    - Freedom Is Made of Simple Stuff--Consent, 1941 Sept. 12 (Film-reel 152)
    - Gene Tierney, 1942 May 19 (Film-reel 152)
    - Hedy Lamarr, 1942 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 152)
    - Ida Lupino, 1942 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 152)
    - Joan Blondell, 1942 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 152)
    - John Carradine, 1942 May 12 (Film-reel 152)
    - Letter from Miss Nelson about "form" of talent letters, 1942 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 152)
    - Letters from Miss Steiger and Hollywood about budget, 1942 Mar. 23; Apr. 13 (Film-reel 152)
    - Lionel Barrymore, 1942 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 152)
    - Look What You Did Christopher--Consent, 1941 Oct. 17 (Film-reel 152)
    - Marlene Dietrich, 1942 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 152)
    - Milton Berle, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 152)
    - Nancy Hawks--Consent, 1941 Nov. 14 (Film-reel 152)
    - New Year's Song--Consent, 1941 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 152)
    - Of Time and River--Consent, 1941 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 152)
    - Parkyakarkus, 1942 Feb. 20; Mar. 24 (Film-reel 152)
      Stage name of comedian and actor Harry Einstein (also known as Harry Parke) (1904-1958)
    - Patsy Kelly, 1942 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 152)
    - Peter Lorre, 1942 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 152)
    - Raymond Walburn, 1942 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 152)
    - Renewals and memos, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 152)
    - Richard Haydn, 1942 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 152)
    - Rosarie Nunez, 1941 June 5 (Film-reel 152)
    - Shirley Ross, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 152)
    - Silence--Consent, 1941 Dec. 5-19 (Film-reel 152)
    - Ted Steele (G. Thorton Steil), 1941 July 25 (Film-reel 152)
    - Television film commercials, 1948 (Film-reel 442)
    - Thanksgiving Proclamation 1938--Consent, 1941 Nov. 21; 28 (Film-reel 152)
    - The Flag and What It Stands Fo--Consent, 1941 Oct. 10 (Film-reel 152)
    - The Little Girl and the Wolf--Consent, 1941 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 152)
    - Thomas Mack, 1942 (Film-reel 152)
    - Walter Huston, 1942 Mar. 31; May 26 (Film-reel 152)
    - William Goodwin, 1941-1942 (Film-reel 152)